{
    "id": "6d2613c4f862470a933d24ca031d2e09",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "James ………………… his frustration by shouting at his mother.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "went on with",
                "gave vent to",
                "gave off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f945845ec2f64dd5a4af734cbb857695"
        },
        {
            "question": "The thief ………………… when he saw the police.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "loped up",
                "loped off",
                "loped out"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "23b7cc7df61d42029c69fb3341decc72"
        },
        {
            "question": "When electricity passes through a salt solution, it will …………………. chemical change.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hold back",
                "bring out",
                "bring about"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "73f9656517304381ba21b5fc6c95fe13"
        },
        {
            "question": "The enquiry commission …………………. him of the charges levelled against him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "intrigued",
                "exonerated",
                "interrogated"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ef3e6ba5a4934c67a1ab2f4c8488de55"
        },
        {
            "question": "Sending man to the moon is ………………… a small achievement.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "by all means",
                "by any means",
                "by no means"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a1f70feae9004a36a807035f42d38c4b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The prince drew ………………… from the stories of great men.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "courage",
                "chivalry",
                "inspiration"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6ea14d5a399d4f309062aaf1ffb983aa"
        },
        {
            "question": "For centuries people belonging to lower castes were ………………. their basic rights.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "discarded of",
                "deprived of",
                "denounced of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fef1c514b5f342f49b722eb13c783206"
        },
        {
            "question": "All geniuses are said to be a bit …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "eccentric",
                "insane",
                "exotic"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "aec7dc2441c142cda867105b5f58cfbf"
        },
        {
            "question": "Many people had to be turned away for ……………….. room.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "want of",
                "because of",
                "wanting"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6eaf58d43ec74fd4b08cde25700e6062"
        },
        {
            "question": "He decided to become a priest ………………….. his father’s objections.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "despite",
                "because",
                "in spite"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a673560186fa4da38c78b95895815570"
        }
    ]
}